Years ago, I took a trip to Egypt,
where I met an old hag named Anyaba.
She told me to fire this
arrow at whoever it desired.
For the Impaled would become my ally.
After the initial shock,
they would witness a unique power rising
up from the deep recesses of their souls.
If memory serves, she
referred to them as Stans.
Jotaro Kujo.
If he and his minion army of Hitman
are pursuing my dear Yoshikage,
then I'll have to create my own army.
One like no other.
An army of stand users.
Here we are, Arrow.
The time's come to select your prey.
Which of these vessels do you desire? Huh?
A telephone pole?
Why would you want a Dolphin?
Wait a minute.
You desire that child?
So you're telling me a child is to
become the first of my new allies?
If that is your will, I'll pierce the
lad's soul and add him to our ranks!
Thank
you
so
much for watching.
That's why I'm
chasing
you
Well, if it isn't our manga
artist extraordinaire.
I hope you're having a good morning, sir.
Hmm, snapping a few photos, eh?
I'm trying to take candid shots of office
workers while on their morning commute.
Just think about it.
Yoshikage Kira, he stole
someone's identity, correct?
Well, he's probably commuting to work
just as his victim once did. You think?
He's between 25 and 35
and nearly 2 meters tall.
Add in that he's an office worker and
our suspect pool dramatically decreases.
I see.
But how can you be sure he
uses this exact station?
He could just as easily commute by car.
That could be the case.
But, though he may have changed his face,
it's very likely that he will
still fall into old habits. Habits.
That'll arouse the suspicion
of his cover family.
By now, they must realize
something's amiss.
My biggest fear is that the family
will recognize their intruder,
prompting him to eliminate them as well.
And don't you think for a
moment that I'm going soft.
I just want to find Kira
before he wreaks more havoc.
Hey, tall bros!
Does one of you want to play
me in a game of Rochambeau?
Rocham!
What are you two deaf or something?
Play with me!
What an oddball. Just play already!
I suppose every station has a
nut job or two running around.
Well, Mr.
Joestar, if you come across any
leads, you know how to reach me.
Don't go sticking your nose in
trouble all by your lonesome now.
Hey, mister.
Aren't you that manga artist?
You stopped drawing for
a little while, right?
I'm a big Shonen Jump
fan, so I know your work.
Now, how about it?
It won't kill you to
play with me, will it?
What is your problem, kid?
Hit the bricks!
But I just want to play
Rochambeau, it'll be fun!
What the?
How peculiar.
The boy's left cheek has a big hole in it.
It's so deep, I bet it
extends into his mouth.
No hard feelings if you win, but...
a drawing we go again.
If you're late, then you lose,
understand? Ready? And...
Ro-sham!
This kid is being weirdly tenacious.
Is he a stand user?
All right, then!
Ro-sham!
Heaven's door, shut this brat up!
Hmm, now let's see.
It says his name is Ken Oyunagi, age 11.
I'm not seeing anything
about him having a stand.
He got the injury when he
fell from a telephone pole.
Hmm, interesting.
He feels compelled to play Rochambeau.
Bizarre, but...
Are you two gentlemen going
to need a ride, or what?
Could we trouble you for 30 more seconds?
Fire away!
Once we do this, you'll
have to leave me be.
Rooshambo!
Well, so long.
How could I lose?
I suppose I've done
enough work for one day.
Yo!
Rohan-sensei!
Are you calling it quits for the day?
Instead of sitting all by
yourself, why don't you join us?
Perfect.
A self-absorbed jerk-off,
a moron, and a bitch.
Three people I have absolutely
nothing in common with.
Hey, guys.
Sorry I'm working at the moment.
Maybe another time.
Oh, gotcha.
Hey, you brat!
What do you think you're doing?
I was going to sit there.
I bet, but you never actually sat down.
The seat was free so I took it.
You snooze you lose, you know what I mean?
I have had enough.
What is your deal?
Let's settle this with Rochambeau.
Winner takes the seat, okay?
Again?
Not fair!
I sat here first so you can't have it!
This is my senior, baby.
Is there a problem here?
Oh, we're fine.
Rohan-sensei, why can't
you give him a break?
Come on, look at him, he's just a kid.
Yeah, I'm with him.
You're supposed to be the mature one.
You could try sitting next to him.
Shut up!
None of you are helping!
Fine, kid.
I'll play with you again.
Well, that's what you're after, isn't it?
Yeah, that's more like it!
Okay, now get ready!
Ro-sham-bo!
Well, would you look at that!
I'm the winner!
Got nothing to say?
I, for one, have never been so happy
to win a game of Rochambeau in my life!
You call this being mature?
There's no better feeling than
destroying a smug whelp at his own game!
Damn!
Lost again!
Oh.
This is some good material.
Who knew such an obscure
book could be found in Mario?
Hm, 7,500 yen.
Do I have that much?
Excuse me, I want to buy this book!
You obnoxious little...
Let's duke it out Rochambeau-style!
Fine.
Brace yourself!
Rochambeau-rock!
You're messing with
the wrong artist, punk!
Look at that! I won!
Still think I'm just a punk?
One win, two losses!
What the hell is going on here?
What is this?
What the...?
It's that damn cheek hole!
So I wasn't off base before!
You might be a user! What?
This is freaking awesome.
I never would have guessed it
was hiding something so cool.
I've never felt anything like the
energy flowing into me right now.
It's totally awesome.
It's like being supercharged.
That's enough.
Now quickly, heaven's door, turn
this little brat into a book.
Judging from his sloppy work,
that must have been the first
time he's used his stand.
However, that doesn't mean he
won't master it given time.
I want to beat the crap out
of Rohan and Rochambeau, huh?
Rochambeau isn't a game of chance.
It's a psychological game of will.
If I beat Rohan at Rochambeau,
it means I've outwilled him.
Rohan's only 20 years old, but
he lives life on his own terms.
His work also inspires
a whole lot of people.
If I can beat the crap out
of Rohan in Rochambeau,
that'll prove I can be
better than him one day.
I can't wait to grow up, because then I'll
be just as respected as the great Rohan.
I knew it!
This kid is well on the road
to becoming a stand user.
The arrow must have just
pierced his soul ability
winning in Rochambeau makes
my opponent's energy my own.
But I must play five games
winning two games only
gives me partial energy
so he needs to win five.
It can't be how did you so this powers
called a stand that's pretty awesome?
Thought you dodged a
bullet there, didn't ya?
Well, think again, because I've already
got a third of your so-called stand!
What?
My right arm is gone!
It sure is, and one third of its
incredible power is under my control!
That means you can't poke
around in my head anymore!
Damn you!
Oh, and if I win two more times,
all of your powers will be mine!
You punk, dammit!
You won't get away with this?!
Taking a swing at me like
that was pretty ballsy.
Guess you got a taste
of your own medicine!
Okay, now I get it.
I have to defeat you in
another game of Rochambeau.
That's the only way I'll win
back my Stan's right arm.
Game on!
Here we go!
Are you completely oblivious
to the plight you're in?
If you lose just one more
time, you're finished.
Surely by now you've realized
you're all out of chances.
Since I know you're a stand
user, I'll show you no mercy.
The moment I retrieve my right arm,
I'm putting you out of commission.
Admit defeat!
Wait, are you trying to psych me out?
Alright, let's get this started.
I'm not ready to play just yet.
I won the last match using paper.
So I guess it's only natural to want
to go with rock or scissors this time.
But it'd be kind of stupid to go
with the obvious just cause...
And it's pretty clear to anyone with eyes
you're not the naive type, Rohan-sensei.
So maybe going with paper
would be the best way to go.
I mean, what could it hurt, right?
Okay, I've made up my mind!
Let's go!
Ro-sham-fo!
What?
I did it!
I outwilled Rohan-sensei
with the power of paper!
That makes two wins and two losses.
Sucks for you.
I just took the lower
half of your heavens door.
If you're tired, you could
rest on that bench over there.
No, that won't be necessary.
When vanquishing your opponent,
you must savor it and look down on
the Concord with pity and disdain.
I've got two wins and two losses, so
we're both one game away from destiny.
But I'm so close to victory,
I can almost taste it!
I know I lost twice, but I came
back and won twice in a row!
It's the other way around for you!
You've lost twice!
You're smack dab in the middle
of a major losing streak!
Marvelous!
As expected from one chosen by
the arrow, we're almost there.
If this kid can finish absorbing
Rohan Kishibe's mind-reading powers,
we'll be unstoppable.
You'll serve my precious Yoshikage well.
Good work.
You've gotten better at the mind games.
Quite impressive for a punk kid.
You've lost the game twice
in a row. That's a fact!
Yes, you're right.
I won't argue.
Since you're big on facts, I take it
you won't mind if I tell you another.
I'm positive you won't be
using paper for this duel.
Guess we'll find out, huh?
Let's not get ahead of ourselves.
I'm not finished yet.
I went with Rock twice,
and it cost me both times.
It's obvious now that Rock is
my unlucky play. Am I wrong?
It goes without saying I'd be adverse to
using Rock again when it's been so unkind.
And since I won't be going with rock this
time, you won't be able to use paper.
Using it would be the same as
admitting I'm not on a losing streak,
despite what you said a while back.
Ha!
You're still gonna lose!
All right, let's do this!
It's time!
Rope! Shamp! Rope!
Oh, that bluffing, and
he still used paper.
What mental fortitude!
There's no way I'm gonna lose to him.
I still have the upper hand in this match.
I'll use paper four times in a row.
This game's in the bag!
Time to go back to rock.
I'll make misfortune work in my favor.
Here we go!
What's wrong with my knees?
Huh?
He's never moved like that before!
The only move Rohan hasn't
used yet is scissors. Crap!
Going with paper four
times in a row is risky!
What? No way!
It seems Rock wasn't unlucky after all.
That bastard! Huh?
No, that's not good!
Hey, mister, can I talk to you?
So, Rohan-sensei, those two
are probably users too, right?
Yeah, I'm right, I can
feel it in my bones.
Let's test my luck.
If it all runs out, those two will
head over here and rescue you.
But if luck is on my side coming over here
will be the last thing on their minds.
Oh, look at that It's Rohan again.
I really can't stand that guy
Let's just smile at him and keep walking.
Well, I suppose we could do that
Their child is?
Yes, he has to be!
One of Rohan's adoring fans.
See you again soon.
Yeah later, man
Well, what do you know?
Seems luck is still on
my side, Rohan-sensei.
So are you scared yet?
I've never felt more
confident about winning!
As long as I've got luck, I can't lose!
I feel like I could play a high-stakes
game of Russian Roulette with
five out of six bullets in the chamber
and still live to tell the epic tale!
Even a shower of glass is nothing to me!
Now then, it's time for the final match.
Who's going to win, Rohan-sensei?
What the heck are you doing?
Hurry and assume your Rochambeau pose.
It's time to play.
You're the one who needs to
hurry up and get started.
I made my move.
You just missed it.
You can knock off the jokes, okay?
It's not a joke.
Well, you said your aim is to surpass me.
But since I'm a bit older, I'll
let you in on a little secret.
Beating one's opponent isn't all that
difficult when you think about it.
What's really challenging is...
And pay attention.
The real challenge is
truly outdoing oneself,
which is what I'm going
to do using my own luck.
Let's go, Rohan!
Time to play!
Oh, chef!
There we go!
How do you like that?
Wait, what's going on? What?
What happened?
Why am I all of a sudden
making the rock move?
That makes three wins and two losses.
Now you've got the unlucky rock.
I couldn't see it before,
but it wasn't just Joseph Joestar
who paid me a visit, luck did too.
The invisible baby.
You put too much energy
into being given luck
while I took it upon
myself to make my own.
That is the very meaning
of outdoing oneself.
Now then, as I recall, I promise
to put you out of commission.
I'm going to write, as long as I
live, I shall lose it, Rochambeau.
And my stand shall be no more, fiend.
Just shut up!
Stay away from me, Rohan!
I swear, if you touch
me, the baby gets it!
You fool!
Do you have any idea
what it is you're doing?
We've moved on now to a war of words!
You didn't really beat me in that match!
You're nothing but a
low-down cheat and a coward!
Give me the baby.
Do it now.
Battle me one more time!
Do that and the baby stays safe and sound!
Are you deaf?
Surrender the baby.
I'll humor you.
Get ready to lose!
Oh, shit, boom, boom, boom!
No!
Why can't I win?
Blast it!
I went through all that trouble to
give you stand powers and you blew it!
Sayonara!
You won't die.
I'm simply going to wipe
your stand out of existence.
No!
I refuse to live life under the
shadow of your stupid writing!
It'd be worse than death!
I won't let you play
around in my head, got it?
I'd rather jump in front
of this giant truck!
Live with that, Rohan!
Bravo, kid, I was wrong about you.
People who have a flair for
the dramatic comic book-like
action I didn't really know how
to bullet the old heartstrings.
What?
But you're gonna get run
over too! I think so.
Where the hell did this
damn wind come from?
Have mercy!
What's this picture?
I can't see!
My view is blown!
What?
It went around us!
You could have been killed, too,
if it hadn't swerved, but you...
Was it... luck?
Perhaps, but I must say you've
become quite an interesting person.
I won't finish you off.
However, you must never
use your stand for evil.
It's just my luck that I
would hit that truck down!
He beat me.
I've completely lost him.
Rohan, wait up! Huh?
Hey, you haven't seen the
baby anywhere, have you?
Yeah, the kid has suddenly gone missing!
Huh?
What if she's turned
fully invisible again?
Damn it, that's right.
Huh? She's gone.
Hey, where are you?
Just pretend like nothing happened.
Uh, hey, where'd you go? Baby?
Rosham Boy.
Real name, Ken Oyanagi.
Stan's name, Boyzman Man,
not out of commission,
though the hole in his cheek remains.
Any time I need to see your
face, it has closed my eyes.
And I am taking two parts
with a crystal mind.
And magenta feeling.
Take a shelter in the face of my spine.
Straight like a chicken cherry cola.
I don't need to try to explain.
I just hold on tight.
And if it happens again,
I'ma move so slightly.
To the arms and the lips and the face.
To the human kind of all that I need to.
I want to.
Come stand a little bit closer.
Breathe in and get a bit higher.
You'll never know what hit you.
When I get to you.
Ooh, I want you.
I don't know if I need you.
Ooh, I gotta find out.
Ooh, I want you.
I don't know if I need you.
Ooh, I gotta find out.